Robert Rauschenberg papers RRFA.01 RRFA.01.TEST
RRF Test Repository
- Printed Materials
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - Exhibitions
      - Solo and Two-Person
        - Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania: "Rauschenberg: Graphic Art", 1970 (Box PM9)
        - Dayton's Gallery 12: "Rauschenberg Currents", 1970 (Box PM14b)
        - Automation House; Castelli Graphics: "Rauschenberg Currents", 1970 (Box PM9)
        - Pasadena Art Museum: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1970 (Box PM9)
        - Minneapolis Institute of Arts: "Robert Rauschenberg: Prints 1948/1970" (Box PM9)
        - Visual Arts Gallery, School of Visual Arts: "Robert Rauschenberg: New Works", 1970 (Box PM14b)
        - Wabash Transit Gallery, School of the Art Institute of Chicago: "Robert Rauschenberg: Syn-Tex Series", 1971 (Box PM14b)
        - Estudio Actual: "Robert Rauschenberg: Autobiografia", 1971 (Box PM9)
        - Dayton's Gallery 12: "Robert Rauschenberg: Syn-Tex Series and Cardbirds, Constructions", 1971 (Box PM9)
        - John Berggruen Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1971 (Box PM9)
        - Multicenter Grafica: "Rauschenberg", 1972 (Box PM9)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Robert Rauschenberg: Tares", 1972 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli and Castelli Graphics: "Made in Tampa: Prints + Clay Pieces", 1972 (Box PM9)
        - Ace Gallery, Los Angeles: "White Paintings", 1973 (Box PM9)
        - Ace Gallery, Vancouver: "White Paintings", 1973 (Box PM9)
        - The Mayor Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Combine Drawings", 1973 (Box PM9)
        - Sonnabend, Paris: "Early Egyptian Series", 1973 (Box PM9)
        - Musée d'Art et d'Industrie: "Robert Rauschenberg, Sarkis Zabunyan", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - The Library Gallery, University of South Florida: "Rauschenberg at Graphicstudio", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Sonnabend, Paris: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1974 (Box PM14b)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Hoarfrost Editions", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - The Israel Museum: "Rauschenberg: Works Made in Israel", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "Robert Rauschenberg and Cy Twombly", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Lucio Amelio: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie Burén: "Robert Rauschenberg: Pages and Fuses", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Los Angeles County Museum of Art: "Robert Rauschenberg's Pages and Fuses", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli and Sonnabend Gallery: "Hoarfrosts", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Hoarfrost Editions", 1974 (Box PM9)
        - Margo Leavin Gallery: "Rauschenberg: Hoarfrost Editions from Gemini G.E.L.", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Dayton's Gallery 12: "Robert Rauschenberg: Hoarfrost Series", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Ace Gallery, Vancouver: "Rauschenberg: Hoarfrost", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie Sonnabend: "Rauschenberg: Hoarfrost", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Bones and Unions", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Visual Arts Museum, School of Visual Arts: "Robert Rauschenberg: Twenty-Six Years of Printmaking", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Museo d'Arte Moderna Ca' Pesaro: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1975 (Box PM14b)
        - Leo Castelli: "Bones and Unions—Ahmedabad, India 1975" (Box PM9)
        - Galerie D: "Rauschenberg: Tampa Drawings", 1976 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie H. M.: "Rauschenberg: Hoarfrost", 1975 (Box PM9)
        - Galleriet: "Rauschenberg: The Bones from Ahmedabad", 1976 (Box PM9)
        - Margo Leavin Gallery and Grunwald Center for Graphic Arts: "Rauschenberg at Gemini: 1967–1976" (Box PM9)
        - Galleriet: "Robert Rauschenberg: The Cardbirds", 1977 (Box PM9)
        - Getler/Pall: "Robert Rauschenberg: Prints", 1977 (Box PM9)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1977 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli; Sonnabend Gallery: "Spreads and Scales", 1977 (Box PM9)
        - Deland Museum: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1977 (Box PM9)
        - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1977 (Box PM10)
        - Albright-Knox Art Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1977 (Box PM10)
        - Janie C. Lee Gallery: "Rauschenberg Hoarfrosts, Jammers, Spreads and Scales", 1977 (Box PM10)
        - Galleriet: "Robert Rauschenberg: Horsefeathers", 1977 (Box PM10)
        - The Art Institute of Chicago: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1977 (Box PM10)
        - Muzeum Narodwe w Warszawie: "Rauschenberg", 1978 (Box PM10)
        - Mayor Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: An Exhibition of Recent Work", 1978 (Box PM10)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Publicons", 1978 (Box PM10)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Publicons", 1978 (Box PM10)
        - Leo Castelli: "Rauschenberg: A Bunch of Prints", 1978 (Box PM14b)
        - Vancouver Art Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Works from Captiva", 1978 (Box PM14b)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "Two New Works by Robert Rauschenberg", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Richard Gray Gallery: "Rauschenberg: New Works", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Richard Hines Gallery: "Spreads and Scales", 1979 (Box PM14b)
        - Fendrick Gallery: "Beyond the Illustrated Book: Rauschenberg's Trace Suspectes", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Kunsthalle Tübingen: "Robert Rauschenberg: Das zeichnerische Werk", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Center for Music, Drama and Art, Lake Placid: "Hiccups", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Musée de Toulon: "Rauschenberg", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Multiples: "Rauschenberg", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "Slides", 1979 (Box PM10)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Robert Rauschenberg: Rookery Mounds Lithographs and Etchings from Glacial Decoy", 1979-1980 (Box PM10)
        - Gallery of Fine Art, Edison Community College: "Rauschenberg", 1980 (Box PM10)
        - Visual Arts Museum, School of Visual Arts: "Variable Editions", 1980 (Box PM14b)
        - Galerie Ileana Sonnabend, Paris: "Robert Rauschenberg: A Portfolio of Twelve Photographs", 1980 (Box PM10)
        - Leo Castelli: "Spreads and Scales", 1980 (Box PM15)
        - Louisiana Museum of Modern Art, Humlebaek: "Rauschenberg: Werke 1950–1980 (Robert Rauschenberg)" (Box PM10)
        - Magnuson Lee Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Lithographs, Etchings and Photographs", 1980 (Box PM10)
        - Galleriet: "Rookery Mounds and More", 1980 (Box PM10)
        - Galerie Watari:"Robert Rauschenberg: A Portfolio of Twelve Photographs", 1981 (Box PM10)
        - Tate Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1981 (Box PM10)
        - Clara Hatton Gallery and Lory Student Center Gallery, Colorado State University: "Rauschenberg in the Rockies", 1981 (Box PM10)
        - Styria Studios: "Arcanum I–XIII", 1981 (Box PM10)
        - Neuberger Museum of Art, Purchase College, State University of New York: "Robert Rauschenberg: Selections from the Permanent Collection", 1981 (Box PM14b)
        - Flow Ace Gallery, 1981 (Box PM10)
        - Leo Castelli Gallery, 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Gallery of Fine Art, Edison Community College: "The First Footage of the 1/4 Mile or 2 Furlong Piece", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Gloria Luria Gallery: "Photems", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Hara Museum of Contemporary Art: "Rauschenberg Print Exhibition", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Robert Rauschenberg: The Razorback Bunch I–VII", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Galleriet: "Arcanum I–XIII", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "7 Characters", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Flow Ace Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Sculpture", 1982 (Box PM10)
        - Aarhus Kunstmuseum, Denmark: "Rauschenberg Fotografier", 1982 (Box PM14b)
        - Leo Castelli; Sonnabend Gallery: "Rauschenberg on Greene Street" (2 folders), 1982 (Box PM15, Box PM14b)
        - Thomas Babeor Gallery: "7 Characters", 1983 (Box PM10)
        - Gallery of Fine Art, Edison Community College: "The Second Footage of the 1/4 Mile or 2 Furlong Piece", 1983 (Box PM10)
        - Rossini Opera Festival: "Rauschenberg Performances 1954/1979", 1983 (Box PM11)
        - Douglas Elliot Gallery: "Rauschenberg Photos", 1983 (Box PM11)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Rauschenberg: Photogravures", 1983 (Box PM11)
        - Marianne Friedland Gallery: "Important Works by Robert Rauschenberg", 1983 (Box PM11)
        - Cooper Union: "Rauschenberg/Performance", 1983 (Box PM11)
        - Gallery of the Port Arthur Public Library: "The Robert Rauschenberg Exhibition", 1984 (Box PM11)
        - Fondation Maeght: "Robert Rauschenberg: Peintures récentes", 1984 (Box PM11)
        - Allen Street Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Photem Series I", 1984 (Box PM11)
        - Fay Gold Gallery: "Rauschenberg and Dine", 1984 (Box PM11)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: New Works", 1984 (Box PM11)
        - Heland Thordén Wetterling Galleries: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1984 (Box PM14b)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1985 (Box PM11)
        - John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art: "Robert Rauschenberg: Works from the Salvage Series", 1985 (Box PM14b)
        - National Art Museum of China: "Rauschenberg Overseas Culture Interchange: ROCI CHINA", 1985 (Box PM11)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Sling-Shots Lit", 1985 (Box PM11)
        - Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston: "Robert Rauschenberg, Work from Four Series: A Sesquicentennial Exhibition", 1985 (Box PM14b)
        - Gallery of Fine Art, Edison Community College: "Rauschenberg: Newest Continuation of the 1/4 Mile or 2 Furlong Piece", 1986 (Box PM11)
        - Visual Arts Museum, School of Visual Arts: "Rauschenberg Photos and Photems", 1986 (Box PM11)
        - Acquavella Contemporary Art: "Robert Rauschenberg: Drawings 1958–1968", 1986 (Box PM11)
        - Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston: "Robert Rauschenberg: Photographs 1949-1984", 1986 (Box PM14b)
        - Galerie Denise René Hans Mayer: "Robert Rauschenberg: Neue Arbeiten", 1987 (Box PM11)
        - BlumHelman Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Works on Paper: 1970–1983", 1987 (Box PM14b)
        - Waddington Galleries: "Robert Rauschenberg: Gluts", 1987 (Box PM11)
        - Heland Wetterling Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Skupturer and Målningar", 1988 (Box PM11)
        - Museo Nacional de Bellas Artes: "Rauschenberg Overseas Culture Interchange: ROCI CUBA", 1988 (Box PM14b)
        - M. Knoedler: "Rauschenberg: New Drawings from the Passes Series", 1988 (Box PM11)
        - BMW Pavilion: "Robert Rauschenberg: Art Car und neue Objekte", 1988 (Box PM14b)
        - Galerie Isy Brachot: "Robert Rauschenberg: Gluts", 1988 (Box PM14b)
        - Galerie Jamileh Weber: "Robert Rauschenberg: Paintings and Gluts", 1988 (Box PM14b)
        - M. Knoedler: "Robert Rauschenberg: Shiners, Gluts, Urban Bourbons", 1988 (Box PM11)
        - Universal Limited Art Editions: "Soviet/American Array", 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Gemini G.E.L.; National Gallery, Yonaga City (Japan), 1989 (Box PM11)
        - DALLAS CARES; Serigraphs, 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Fabian Carlsson Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Akira Ikeda Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: New Paintings", 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Schwartz Cierlak Gallery: "Prints 1965-1982", 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Fred Hoffman Gallery and Manny Silverman Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg, The Gemini Works: 1967–1988", 1989 (Box PM14b)
        - M. Knoedler: "Robert Rauschenberg: Works", 1989 (Box PM11)
        - Projects Room, Scott Hanson Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: China Mix", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Galerie Montaigne: "Peintures, Dessins, Editions", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Rauschenberg: Currents '70", 1990 (Box PM11, Box PM15)
        - M. Knoedler: "Robert Rauschenberg: Works on Paper", 1990 (Box PM15)
        - Runkel-Hue-Williams; Lang and O'Hara: "Robert Rauschenberg: Paintings 1962–1980", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Galerie Fabien Boulakia: "Rauschenberg", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Galleri Lempertz Contempora: "Robert Rauschenberg: Prints 1969–1970", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Fondation Vincent Van Gogh: "Roy Lichtenstein, Robert Rauschenberg: 38 Oeuvres gravées de 1965 à 1989", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Feigen: "Robert Rauschenberg: Gluts", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Scott Hanson Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Paintings 1962–1970", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Galerie Baudoin Leon: "Robert Rauschenberg Polaroids", 1990 (Box PM11)
        - Galleria d'arte il Gabbiano: "Robert Rauschenberg: Dipinti recenti", 1991 (Box PM11)
        - Appiani Arte Trentadue: "Robert Rauschenberg: Dipinti recenti", 1992 (Box PM11)
        - Simmons Visual Arts Center, Brenau University: "Robert Rauschenberg: Print Survey in Themes, 1952–1992" (Box PM11)
        - Leeds Gallery, University of Texas at Austin: "Robert Rauschenberg: Prints from the Art Collection of the Harry Ransom Humanities Research Center", 1992 (Box PM11)
        - M. Knoedler: "Rauschenberg: Bicycloids, Urban Bourbons + Eco-Echo", 1993 (Box PM11)
        - Kunstsammlung Nordrhein-Westfalen: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1994 (Box PM11)
        - Wetterling Teo Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: New Works", 1996 (Box PM11)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "Rauschenberg: Carnal Clocks, Cardboards, Jammers", 1996 (Box PM12)
        - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum: "Robert Rauschenberg: A Retrospective", 1997 (Box PM12)
        - Gemini G.E.L.: "Darryl Pottorf/Robert Rauschenberg: Marrakitch, Quattro Mani/Marrakech, The Moroccan Series", 2000 (Box PM12)
        - Versicherungskammer Bayern: "Rauschenberg: Posters", 2001 (Box PM12)
        - Eckert Fine Art: "Robert Rauschenberg: Beamers", 2002 (Box PM12)
        - Galerie Jamileh Weber: "Robert Rauschenberg: Japanese Recreational Clayworks", 2002 (Box PM12)
        - Palazzo dei Diamanti: "Rauschenberg", 2004 (Box PM12)
        - University Art Gallery, California State University: "Robert Rauschenberg, Artist-Citizen: Posters for a Better World", 2004-2005 (Box PM12)
        - DJT Fine Art: "Robert Rauschenberg: Primarily Prints", 2005 (Box PM12)
        - Jonathan O'Hara Gallery: "Robert Rauschenberg: Transfer Drawings from the 1960s", 2007 (Box PM12)
        - Craig F. Starr Associates: "Accident: Rauschenberg's Printmaking Breakthrough, 1962–65", 2007 (Box PM12)